It ends here
Taken 3 is a thriller, action film directed by Olivier Megaton.
Ex-government operative Bryan Mills finds his life is shattered when
he's falsely accused of a murder that hits close to home.
As he's pursued by a savvy police inspector, Mills employs his particular set of
skills to track the real killer and exact his unique brand of justice.
Bryan Mills, played by Liam Neeson.
Inspector Frank Dotzler, played by Forest Whitaker.
Kim Mills, played by Maggie Grace.
Stuart St. John, played by Dougray Scott.
Lenore St. John, played by Famke Janssen.
Oleg Malankov, played by Sam Spruell.
Taken 3 (sometimes stylized as TAK3N) is a 2015
English-language French action-thriller film.
It is the third in the Taken trilogy, starring Liam
Neeson as former government operative Mills.
It was directed by Olivier Megaton and written by
Luc Besson and Robert Mark Kamen.
The cast also includes Forest Whitaker, Maggie Grace, and Famke Janssen.
Mills is falsely accused of murder, gets tracked by a police inspector and uses
his skill set to prove his innocence and find the real murderer.
Taken 3 was released in France on 21 January 2015 by EuropaCorp Distribution.
The film received generally negative reviews from critics, who found it was hindered by uninspired action
scenes, unclear direction, and a formulaic storyline and that the franchise had run its course.
It grossed $326 million.
The film explores themes of california, escape, funeral, gas station, detective.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking and intense.